redoute.com 2017-07-11

# | La Redoute

Collection, treatment and archiving of personal data: In an attempt to perform efficiently its obligations, LA REDOUTE must collect certain personal information about the User (surname, first name, email address and home address). By giving to LA REDOUTE his/her email address, the User will be able to receive an email acknowledging his/her orders.

LA REDOUTE is obliged by the law to check the accuracy and ensure the updating of the personal data that it had collected. Therefore, the User is entitled to access, modify and delete his/her personal information. The User is informed that this automatic data processing, (especially the management of email addresses), has been declared.

LA REDOUTE strives to ensure the confidentiality and security of the data transmitted on the Web. In this respect, please note that the website LaRedoute.com utilises a secure payment mode, called Secure Socket Layer (SSL). In an attempt to train our Customer’s service and for quality’s monitoring purposes, please note that certain phone calls may be recorded. Further, certain data may be processed in Switzerland for the management of Users calls purposes. Subscription to the newsletter: Depending on his/her choice made at the registration stage, the User may receive commercial offers from LA REDOUTE as business partners, via emails, telephone or text messages as specified at the time of the registration.

The User may change his/her minds at any time by going to the section “My space/ I modify my personal data/ LA REDOUTE newsletter” where he/she shall tick “ I am not interested in the commercial offers and I do no longer wish to receive them”.

COOKIES - Cookies are small files downloaded on your computer (or any other terminal used for the access to the website). Cookies enables websites to provide you a personnal navigation by memorizing your parameters. Cookies enables you to get a more personal navigation on the websites by memorzing some of the parameters you chose during your last visit. Cookies do not damage your computer. For further informations, you can visit www.allaboutcookies.org. Cookies enables us to provide you a more personnalized and comfortable navigation. We do not use cookies to register informations such as your name, your adress or your bank account informations.

We use cookies for your navigation (keep your session active, and not to ask you to put the same products in the basket if you left for few minutes for example), to personnalize the website for you (with your langage and country, for example), to collect statistics or for 3rd parties (if we need to pay a commission after you clicked on a banners for example). Most of the browsers accepts cookie except if you parametered it not to accept it.

By visiting this website, you accept the cookies to be used according this policy. If you are willing to refuse, you can either desactivate your cookies, or not visiting the site.
